Finding aid for the Friends of the Los Angeles River records, 1987-2013 LSC.2215
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 2: Research Materials, 1941-2014
  - Flood Control, 1938 (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - Flood Control, 1941-2011 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Flood Control, 1983-1997 (Box 64, Folder 1-2)
  - Flood Control Channel Dangers, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - FoLAR background, 1970-2004 (Box 90, Folder 5-7)
  - Foundation Partners, 2001-2005 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Grants, 1996-2009 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Groundwater, 1990-2003 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - High Speed Rail, 2009 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - History of Los Angeles River, 1941-2007 (Box 42, Folder 1-2)
  - Industrial Area Plans, 2006 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Industrial Area and Watershed Data/Reports, 2006-2008 (Box 158, Folder 11)
  - Integrated Resources Plan, 2005-2007 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Integrated Resources Plan- Wastewater, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Jennifer Price, 2001-2007 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Jim Danza, 1983-1992 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Land Use, 1978-2009 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Land Use Committee, 2007-2009 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Los Angeles Conservancy Tour Guides, 1994-1997 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Los Angeles County Drainage Area, 1985-1997 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Los Angeles County Drainage Area, 1985-1997 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Los Angeles County Drainage Area Project EIR, 1994-1996 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Los Angeles County Drainage Area Project EIR Appendices, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 3-4)
  - Los Angeles County Drainage Area Project Feasibility Study, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Los Angeles County Drainage Area Project Feasibility Study, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 4-5)
  - Los Angeles County Drainage Area Project- Long Beach, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Los Angeles County Integrated Regional Water Management Plan, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Los Angeles Country Transportation Reports (Taylor Yard, East-West Corridor, Arroyo Seco Parkway), 1993-2001 (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - Los Angeles Country Water Management Policy, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Los Angeles Downtown Strategic Plan, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Los Angeles Regional Dredge Plan (U.S. Army Corps), 2008 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Los Angeles River and Runoff Press Clippings, 1997-2011 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Los Angeles River Bridges, 1999-2012 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Los Angeles River Bridges, 1997-2012 (Folder 158, Box 4)
  - Los Angeles River Bridges, 2000 (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - Los Angeles River District Maps & 1940 General Plan, undated (Box 158, Folder 10)
  - Los Angeles River Copper Water Study, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 3-4)
  - Los Angeles River Flood Control, 1993-2013 (Box 64, Folder 3-5)
  - Los Angeles River Flood Control, 1993-2013 (Box 65, Folder 1-2)
  - Los Angeles River Flooding Photos, undated (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Los Angeles River Greenbelt, 1989-2013 (Box 41, Folder 11-12)
  - Los Angeles River Master Plan, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Los Angeles River Master Plan, 2006 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Los Angeles River Master Plan Landscape Drawings, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Los Angeles River Master Plan Update, 1998-2006 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Los Angeles River Master Plan with Notes, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Los Angeles River Master's Thesis (Dermitzel), 1993 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Los Angeles River Park Pathway, 1990-1991 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Los Angeles River Photos, 1990s (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Los Angeles River Photos, 1980s (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Los Angeles River Photos, undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Los Angeles River Photos, undated (Box 48, Folder 4-5)
  - Los Angeles River Rescue Task Force, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Los Angeles River Revitalization Master Plan (Draft), 2007 (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - Los Angeles River Revitalization Master Plan, 2007 (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - Los Angeles River Site Descriptions, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Los Angeles River Watershed Monitoring Program, 2009 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Los Angeles Unified Schools, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Los Angeles Water/Land Restoration Projects, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Manuscripts and Articles, 1988-1994 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Maps, 1990-2005 (Box 48, Folder 6-7)
  - Master Plan for Urban Runoff Stakeholders, 2007 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Milken Families Foundation, c. 1990 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Million Trees Los Angeles, 2001 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Research Materials, 1995-2003 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Misc. Los Angeles River Photos, undated (Box 158, Folder 6)
  - Misc. Posters & Maps, undated (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - Misc. River Site Designs, 1985-1990 (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - Natural Habitat Report for FoLAR, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters and Journals, 1992-2011 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters and Journals: ALERT- Journal for Non-profit Managers, 2004-2007 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters and Journals: California Coast and Ocean Journal, 1992-2008 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Newsletters and Journals: City of Los Angeles Publications, 1990-2007 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Newsletters and Journals: Creek Currents (Urban Creek Council), 1990 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Newsletters and Journals: Currents (Heal the Bay Journal), 2005-2008 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters and Journals: Environment Journal, 2006 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Newsletters and Journals: Environmental Media Association, 2002-2008 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters and Journals: Environmental Protection Agency Journal, 1995-2011 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Newsletters and Journals: Food and Water Journal, 2000 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Newsletters and Journals: Forest and River News (Trees Foundation), 2008-2010 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Newsletters and Journals: Form- Pioneering Design Magazine, 2011 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Newsletters and Journals: Getty Conservation Institute Newsletter, 1998 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Newsletters and Journals: Headwaters (Friends of the River Journal), 1990-2008 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Newsletters and Journals: Metro Quarterly, 2007-2008 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Newsletters and Journals: Mono Lake Newsletter, 2000-2007 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Newsletters and Journals: River Network Publications, 1992-2011 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters and Journals: River Partner Journal, 2005-2010 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters and Journals: Southern Sierran Newsletter, 1992-2013 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Newsletters and Journals: Storm Water Solutions Journal, 2010 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Newsletters and Journals: Symbiosis Journal, 2012-2013 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Newsletters and Journals: The Griffith Reporter, 2013 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Newsletters and Journals: The Planning Report, 1994-2004 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - Newsletters and Journals: The River Reporter (Chicago River), 2004-2010 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters and Journals: Valley Habitats Newsletter, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Newsletters and Journals: Volunteer Monitor Newsletter, 1992-2008 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Newsletters and Journals: Water Efficiency Journal, 2008 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters and Journals: Watershed Events Newsletter, 2002-2003 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters and Journals: Watershed Wise Newsletter, 2002-2014 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Nonprofit Management, 1991-2008 (Box 44, Folder 5-6)
  - Nonprofit Management, 2003-2011 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Other Rivers, 1990-2006 (Box 45, Folder 2-6)
  - Other Rivers, 1990-2006 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Other Rivers Photos, 1990-2006 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Pacific Pipeline, 1991-1993 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Photo Calendars of Los Angeles (Tom LaBonge), 2010-2011 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Press Clippings, 1940s (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Press Clippings, 1980s (Box 79, Folder 2-5)
  - Press Clippings: First FoLAR Article, 1989 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Press Clippings, 1990 (Box 80, Folder 1-3)
  - Press Clippings, 1991 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Press Clippings, 1992 (Box 81, Folder 1-2)
  - Press Clippings, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Press Clippings, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Press Clippings, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Press Clippings, 1996 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Press Clippings, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Press Clippings, 1998 (Box 82, Folder 3-4)
  - Press Clippings, 1999 (Box 83, Folder 1-3)
  - Press Clippings, 2000 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Press Clippings, 2001 (Box 84, Folder 1-2)
  - Press Clippings, 2002 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Press Clippings, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 4-5)
  - Press Clippings, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Press Clippings, 2005 (Box 85, Folder 2-3)
  - Press Clippings, 2006 (Box 85, Folder 4-5)
  - Press Clippings, 2006 (Box 86, Folder 1-3)
  - Press Clippings, 2007 (Box 86, Folder 4-5)
  - Press Clippings, 2007 (Box 87, Folder 1-2)
  - Press Clippings, 2008 (Box 87, Folder 3-4)
  - Press Clippings, 2009 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Press Clippings, 2010-2013 (Box 88, Folder 1-2)
  - Press Clippings, undated (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Press Clippings, 1989-2013 (Box 142, Folder 1-2)
  - Press Clippings, 1989-2011 (Box 143, Folder 1-2)
  - Press Clippings, 1992-2013 (Box 144, Folder 1-2)
  - Press Clippings, 1994-2001 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Press Clippings, 2011-2013 (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Press Clippings, 2013 (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Population and Habitat Education, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 4-5)
  - Proposed Art Activities, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Public Land Trusts, 1993-2008 (Box 68, Folder 5-6)
  - Publications, undated (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - Quality Assurance Project Plan, 1995-2002 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Rail Projects, 2009-2012 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Railroad spikes, undated (Box 152)
  - Reclaimed Water, 1990-2010 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Recreational Land Use, 1996-2011 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Research Posters (Box 155)
  - Riparian Habitat, 1989-2001 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - River Advocacy Study (Draft), 1993 (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - Rivers/Landscape Design, 1989-2012 (Box 42, Folder 5-6)
  - Riverwatch Data Entry, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Riverwatch Monitoring Equipment, 1988-2003 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Riverwatch Site Maps, undated (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Riverwatch Training, 2000-2003 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Riverwatch Water Monitoring, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Runoff, 2000-2005 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Salmonid Conference, Santa Barbara, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Sewers, 1990s (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Sites: Arroyo Seco, 1999-2012 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Sites: Ballona Creek, 2001-2006 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Sites: Burbank, 2012 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Sites: Chinatown/Cornfield, 1998-2007 (Box 71, Folder 4-5)
  - Sites: Chinatown Yard Photographs, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Sites: Compton Creek, 1995-2009 (Box 71, Folder 6-7)
  - Sites: Juan Bautista de Anza National Historic Trail, 1990-2010 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Sites: Las Virgines Water District Report, 1999 (Box 72, Folder 1-2)
  - Sites: Long Beach, 1993-2006 (Box 72, Folder 3-5)
  - Sites: Long Beach, 1993-2006 (Box 73, Folder 1-4)
  - Sites: Long Beach, 1993-2006 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Sites: Malibu Creek, 1997-1998 (Box 74, Folder 2-3)
  - Sites: Playa Vista, 1997 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Sites: Port of Los Angeles, 2005-2009 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Sites: San Pedro, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Sites: Santa Monica Bay, 1988-2004 (Box 75, Folder 2-4)
  - Sites: Sepulveda Basin, 2002-2013 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Sites: Sepulveda Wetlands Park, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Sites: Studio City, 2012-2013 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Sites: Taylor Yard, 1990-2004 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Sites: Taylor Yard, 1992-1993 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Sites: Taylor Yard, 1990-2004 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Sites: Topanga, 1996 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Sites: Tujunga Wash, 1978-2000 (Box 76, Folder 4-5)
  - Sites: Tujunga Wash, 1978-2000 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Sites: Universal City, 1996-2010 (Box 77, Folder 2-4)
  - Sites: Universal City, 1996-2010 (Box 78, Folder 1-2)
  - Sites: Verdugo Wash, 1996 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Sites: Watts, 2008 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Sites: Whittier Narrows Flood Basin, 1996 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Sixth Street Viaduct Seismic Project, 2011 (Box 89, Folder 6-7)
  - Soil/Erosion Control, 1983-1995 (Box 63, Folder 1-5)
  - Southern California Coastal Water Research, 1986-1987 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Southern California Marine Institute Training, undated (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Stormwater Management, 1991-2005 (Box 56, Folder 1-2)
  - Stormwater/Urban Runoff, 1990s (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Stream/River Restoration, 1988-2003 (Box 46, Folder 2-4)
  - Superfund Sites, 1992-2007 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Total Maximum Daily Load, 1999-2009 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Total Maximum Daily Load, 2000 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Transportation, 1992-2003 (Box 61, Folder 1-2)
  - Urban Los Angeles River Photos, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Urban Rangers, 2011 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Urban Waterways Restoration Training Manual, 1996 (Box 59, Folder 1-2)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, 1992-2008 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Army Corps Los Angeles River Estuary Dredging, 1998 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Army Corps Los Angeles River Estuary Dredging, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Army Corps-Verdugo Wash, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - USC Course on Los Angeles River, undated (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Volunteer Training Materials, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Wastewater, 1990-2010 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Water Engineering, 1990s (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Water Monitoring, 1987-2009 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Water Plan and Policy, 1983-1998 (Box 65, Folder 4-5)
  - Water Plan and Policy, 1983-1998 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Water Quality, 1981-2004 (Box 52, Folder 3-5)
  - Water Quality, 1986-2004 (Box 53, Folder 1-2)
  - Water Quality Monitoring, 1987-2009 (Box 51, Folder 1-5)
  - Water Rights/Dams, 1976-2006 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Watershed Management, 1996-2011 (Box 54, Folder 2-4)
  - Watersheds, 1992-2008 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Watersheds, 1992-2008 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Wetlands, 1992-2011 (Box 58, Folder 1-3)
  - Wildlife, 1990-2009 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Series 3: Legal Records, 1990-2011
  This series is comprised of correspondence, notes, legal filings, and administrative records concerning various sites and proposed projects along the river. Documents relating to legislation include those concerning the Los Angeles City Council, California State Senate, and California Assembly bills, as well as federal legislation, such as the Clean Water Act. This series also includes filings, pleadings, correspondence, notes, environmental impact reports, and comments for several legal cases, such as the case pertaining to the Los Angeles County Drainage Area Project, FoLAR, et al. v. Majestic Realty, and FoLAR v. Lennar.
  - Anheuser-Busch Spill Settlement, 1991-1992 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Big Tujunga Wash Golf Course, 1995-1997 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Burbank-Glendale Rail Transit Project, 1993-1994 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Chatten-Brown Invoices, 1994-2002 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - California Regional Water Quality Control Board, 1990-1993 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - California Regional Water Quality Control Board, 1994-1999 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - California Regional Water Quality Control Board, 2000 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - California Regional Water Quality Control Board, 2001 (Box 121, Folder 1-2)
  - California Regional Water Quality Control Board, 2002-2010 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Cases: Cast-Rite Corporation, 1996 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Cases: FoLAR Intervention in L.A. v. Water Boards, 2000 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Cases: Los Angeles Zoo Wastewater Treatment Facility, 1999 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Cases: Studio City Senior Housing, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Cornfields: Correspondence, 1999 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Cornfields: Correspondence, 2000-2002 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Elected Officials: Correspondence, 1990-2011 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Elected Officials: Miscellaneous, 1990-2006 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - FoLAR et al. v. County of L.A. et al.: Administrative Records, 1995 (Box 135, Folder 1-3)
  - FoLAR et al. v. County of L.A. et al.: Administrative Records, 1995 (Box 136, Folder 1-3)
  - FoLAR et al. v. County of L.A. et al.: Administrative Records, 1995 (Box 137, Folder 1-4)
  - FoLAR et al. v. County of L.A. et al.: Administrative Records, 1995 (Box 138, Folder 1-3)
  - FoLAR et al. v. County of L.A. et al.: Administrative Records, 1995 (Box 139, Folder 1-2)
  - FoLAR et al. v. County of L.A. et al.: Supplemental Records, 1996 (Box 139, Folder 3-4)
  - FoLAR et al. v. County of L.A. et al.: Supplemental Records, 1996 (Box 140, Folder 1-3)
  - FoLAR v. Lennar et al., 2001 (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - FoLAR v. Lennar et al.: Correspondence and Notes Vol. I and II, 2000-2001 (Box 130, Folder 1-3)
  - FoLAR v. Lennar et al.: Correspondence and Notes Vol. I and II, 2000-2001 (Box 129, Folder 4-5)
  - FoLAR v. Lennar et al.: Correspondence and Notes Vol. III, 2000-2001 (Box 130, Folder 4-5)
  - FoLAR v. Lennar et al.: Notes, 2001 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - FoLAR v. Lennar et al.: Pleadings Vol. I, 2000-2002 (Box 127, Folder 1-5)
  - FoLAR v. Lennar et al.: Pleadings Vol. I, 2000-2002 (Box 128, Folder 1-3)
  - FoLAR v. Lennar et al.: Pleadings Vol. II, 2000-2001 (Box 128, Folder 4-5)
  - FoLAR v. Lennar et al.: Pleadings Vol. III, 2000-2002 (Box 129, Folder 1-3)
  - FoLAR v. Lennar et al.: Research, 1998-2000 (Box 131, Folder 5-6)
  - FoLAR v. Lennar et al.: Responses to Comments, 2000 (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - FoLAR v. Lennar et al.: Traffic Impact Study, 1999 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - FoLAR et al. v. Majestic Realty, 1999-2000 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - FoLAR et al. v. Majestic Realty: Electronic Mail, 2000 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - FoLAR et al. v. Majestic Realty: Pleadings Vol. I, 2000-2001 (Box 123, Folder 3-5)
  - FoLAR et al. v. Majestic Realty: Pleadings Vol. II, 2000-2001 (Box 124, Folder 1-2)
  - FoLAR et al. v. Majestic Realty: Pleadings Vol. III, 2000-2001 (Box 124, Folder 3-4)
  - FoLAR et al. v. Majestic Realty: Correspondence Vol. VI, 2000-2001 (Box 125, Folder 4-5)
  - FoLAR et al. v. Majestic Realty: Correspondence Vol. VII, 2000-2001 (Box 126, Folder 1-2)
  - FoLAR et al. v. Majestic Realty: Correspondence Vol. VIII, 2000-2001 (Box 126, Folder 3-4)
  - FoLAR et al. v. Majestic Realty: Correspondence Vol. IX, 2000-2002 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - FoLAR et al. v. Majestic Realty: Settlement, 2000-2001 (Box 125, Folder 2-3)
  - General Auto Wrecking Consent Decree, 1994-1998 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Heal the Bay et al. v. L.A. County Department of Public Works, 1995-1996 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Heal the Bay et al. v. L.A. County Department of Public Works, 1995 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Heal the Bay et al. v. L.A. County Department of Public Works: Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 122, Folder 7-8)
  - Heal the Bay et al. v. L.A. County Department of Public Works: Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Legacy: Taylor Yard, 1998 (Box 132, Folder 1-2)
  - Legacy: Taylor Yard, 2000-2001 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Legislation, 1992-2004 (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Legislation: CA AB 350, 1990-2000 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Legislation: CA AB 1355, 1999 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Legislation: CA Assembly Hearing on Coastal Infrastructure, 1997 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Legislation: CA SB 20 + 20x, 1992 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Legislation: CA SB 754, 1999 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Legislation: CA SB 1188, 1997 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Legislation: CA SB 1201, 2012 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Legislation: CA SB 2010, 1998 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Legislation: CA State and Assembly (Miscellaneous), 1990-2010 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Legislation: Clean Water Act, 1999-2008 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Legislation: Federal (Miscellaneous), 1992-1997 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Legislation: LA River Advisory Council, 2000 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Legacy Partners Mitigation Agreement, 1998-2003 (Box 122, Folder 5-6)
  - Legislation: Propositions, 1996-2003 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Legislation: Proposition O, 2005 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Los Angeles City Council, 1992-2012 (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Los Angeles County Drainage Area Project (LACDA), 1990-1992 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - Los Angeles County Drainage Area Project (LACDA), 1993 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Los Angeles County Drainage Area Project (LACDA), 1994 (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - Los Angeles County Drainage Area Project (LACDA), 1995 (Box 134, Folder 1-2)
  - Los Angeles County Drainage Area Project (LACDA), 1996-1999 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Los Angeles County Drainage Area (LACDA): Administrative Records Index, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Los Angeles County Drainage Area Project (LACDA): Comments, 1993 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Los Angeles County Drainage Area (LACDA): EIR, 1994 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Los Angeles County Drainage Area (LACDA): EIR Appendix, 1994 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Los Angeles County Drainage Area Project (LACDA): Faxes, 1995-1996 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Los Angeles County Drainage Area Project (LACDA): Flood Insurance, 1992-1996 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Los Angeles County Drainage Area Project(LACDA): FoLAR et al. v. County of L.A., 1995-1997 (Box 132, Folder 4-5)
  - Los Angeles County Drainage Area Project (LACDA): FoLAR et al. v. County of L.A., 1995-1997 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Los Angeles County Drainage Area Project (LACDA): L.A. River Watershed Task Force, 1995 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Los Angeles County Drainage Area (LACDA): Revisions to Feasibility Report, 1992 (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Los Angeles Turf Club SEP, 2000-2002 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Marine Life Protection Act, 2009 (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Universal Studios Project, 1995-1997 (Box 118, Folder 5)
- Series 4: Activities, 1930-2013
  This series contains meeting minutes, agendas, notes, correspondence, photographs, press clippings, meeting and exhibit announcements, press releases, and conference schedules related to the events and programs developed and held by FoLAR. Topics include watershed management and flood control; the establishment of educational activities, such as Eco-Heroes and the River School; and recaps of events and programs, as covered in FoLAR's newsletter, Current Events. Also touched upon are outreach and river awareness events, including public mural projects and art exhibits, such as Leo Limon's River Katz; dance, drama, and poetry events; tours of the river, including Down by the Los Angeles River Walks; coastal and river clean ups; and awards and fiesta dinners. Organizations represented in these materials include the United States Army Corps of Engineers and the Los Angeles and San Gabriel Rivers Watershed Council.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by subject. Folders with materials related to the FoLAR newletters, river cleanups, and the awards and fiesta dinners are further arranged chronologically.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  RESTRICTED ACCESS: Use of audio and moving image material requires production of listening and viewing copies.
  - Activities: Clean-Up Bags, 2011-2013 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Activities: Long Beach River Conference, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Activities: Los Angeles River Cooperation Committee, 2011 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Activities: Los Angeles River Recreation Photos, undated (Box 158, Folder 8)
  - Activities: Los Angeles River Tours, 2001-2003 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Activities: Los Angeles River Tours, 2001-2007 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Activities: Misc. Educational Displays, undated (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Activities: Misc. Event Announcements Original Artwork/Proofs, undated (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Activities: Misc. Event Announcements Printed Samples, undated (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - Activities: Misc. Events Artwork & Printed Samples, undated (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Activities: Original Artwork/Proofs for Misc. Event Announcements, circa 2005 (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - Activities: Rancho Palos Verde Site, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Activities: River Clean Up Photos, undated (Box 158, Folder 7)
  - Activities: Ulysses Guide Book to the L.A. River, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Advocacy: Amtrak/Caltrans Los Angeles River Force, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)